[
  {
    "question": "Which country won the first-ever Cricket World Cup in 1975?",
    "answer" : "West indies"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who holds the record for the fastest century in ODI/T20 cricket?",
    "answer" : "AB de villiers in 31 balls/ chris gayle in 30 balls."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which cricketer has taken the most wickets in Test matches?",
    "answer" : "Muttiah Muralitharan 800 wickets."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which cricketer has taken the most wickets in Test matches?",
    "answer" : "Muttiah Muralitharan 800 wickets."
  },
  {
    "question": "In which year was the Indian Premier League (IPL) launched?",
    "answer" : "2008"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the only player to have scored 10,000 runs in Test matches?",
    "answer" : "Sachin Tendulkar"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the only cricketer to have scored 100 international centuries?",
    "answer": "Sachin Tendulkar with virat standing next to him with 80 centuries."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which bowler holds the record for the most wickets in a single ODI World Cup?",
    "answer": "Mtchell starc with 27 wickets." 
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the only cricketer to have scored a century in all three formats of the game?",
    "answer": "Suresh Raina"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which cricketer has the most runs in T20 International cricket?",
    "answer": "Virak kohli"
  }
]